<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>org.WabiAnimation.Kraken</id>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">kraken.desktop</launchable>
    <name>Kraken</name>
    <summary>Free and open source 3D creation suite</summary>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>Proprietary</project_license>
    <description>
        <p>
            Kraken is the future of 3D graphics for film, animation, and the
            future of interactive digital experiences. It supports a Hydra
            Powered Viewport capable of rendering any engine from Arnold,
            to Renderman, a real-time, physically based render engine called
            PHOENIX and many more production tools are coming soon.
        </p>

        <p>
            Currently in development is a wide range of procedural tools such as
            a modeler, rigger, animation framework, simulation engine, render farm
            integrator, interprocess framework, and more. Built upon the Pixar
            Production pipeline, and ready to blow a hole in your GPU. We're just
            as excited as you are to kick this off to brand-new heights.
        </p>

        <p>
            Kraken is in it's very early development stages. Join the development
            fund and help us evolve Kraken over the next several years. Together
            we can build the future of animation, and build the tools the way we
            want to use them. Development is moving rapidly and we are consistantly
            supporting new tools as they are made available. Drop us a line and
            we'll be happy to implement all sorts of community driven ideas.
        </p>

        <p>
            Let's fly.
        </p>
    </description>
    <url type="homepage">https://www.kraken.xyz</url>
    <url type="help">https://www.kraken.xyz/support/</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://developer.kraken.xyz</url>
    <url type="donation">https://www.kraken.xyz/development-fund/</url>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>#</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>#</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>#</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>#</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
        <release version="1.00" date="2020-12-18">
            <description>
                <p>New features:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Arnold Render Engine</li>
                    <li>Renderman Render Engine</li>
                    <li>Interactive Viewport</li>
                    <li>Message Bus</li>
                    <li>Server Spool</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Enhancements:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Extremely Interactive Feedback</li>
                    <li>Hotkey Fixups</li>
                    <li>Begin Modeler Project</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
  </releases>
</component>
